ILGWU Communications Department Photographs 5780/176 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Eastern Pennsylvania (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Includes Workers at Tina Fashions in Nazareth, PA on strike, 1987; Parade for Constitution's bicentennial, 1987; Workers of Six Eleven, picketing, 1988; Richard Drabic of Valley Youth House, 1987; Eastern District Council ILGers, n.d.; Shirley Ziegman, chairperson of T & T Sportswear, Phillipsburg, NJ, n.d; Workers of United Paperworkers Local 1787, 1988; Billboard advertisement for Nicky-Lynn Sportswear with ILGWU logo and union member, Eastern PA, 1988; Eastern, PA. District ILGers in Washington, D.C., 1988; ILGers get lesson in police drug policy, 1988; Earl Laub, Eastern District manager, 1988; V.P. Joseph Fisher, manager of the Philadelphia-South Jersey District, 1987; ILGers who supported the NFL during strike, Philadelphia, 1987; ILGers in opposition to Robert Bork's nomination to the Supreme Court, 1987; Members of Local 111 in Allentown; 1987; ILGWU Assistant Director Jay Levine, 1987; ILGers participate in Red Cross training, 1987; Sam Cavalieri, assistant manager of Allentown, PA, with Irwin Solomon, Ike Gordon, Joseph Fisher, Roseann Heydt and Earl Laub, 1987; ILGers in Easton, PA at the Penn State Union Leadership Academy classes, 1986; Gail Meyer, ILGWU Business Agent for the Eastern Pennsylvania Region and president of the Northampton County Labor Council with Earl Laub, Meyer, Evelyn Dubrow and Joe Fisher, 1986; Union members in Easton, PA., 1986; Liberty Bell; Carpenters Hall, Philadelphia
- Education Department and Activities (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Includes Jim Young, president, Harrisburg Central Labor Council, John C. Frye, director, Education and Community Services Activities, PA AFL-CIO, Juliet Rowland, president, United Way of the Capital Region; William Sprandel, chairperson, Community Services Committee of Harrisburg Labor Council, Robert Settle, United Way, 1995; Exec. V.P. Edgar Romney, NYC, 1995; ILGWU Vice Pres. Evelyn Dubrow, Pres. Jay Mazur, Romney, NYC, 1993; Participants of the Worker-Family Education Program Cultural Week, NYC, 1994; ILGers in Matawan, NJ, 1993; ILGWU students, Ohio, 1986; ILGers, Storrs, CT., 1994; ILGers learning art, NYC, 1992; Bruce Herman, president of the Garment Industry Development Corp., and Phil Kelman, project director of the Fashion Institute of Technology, 1991; Teachers help ILG parents, 1991; with Exec. V.P. Romney and Pres. Jay Mazur, NYC, 1988; ILGers receive high school equivalency degrees, NYC, 1988; Advertisements for PBS specials on labor history, 1986; ILGers receive education awards, 1986
- Essay Contest (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Includes Winners: Santa Rivera, Carol, Morre Wexler, Myrtle Tolley, Catherine O'Neill & Ann Centrone, 1988
- Garment Workers & A Whole Lot More (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Includes Workers at Eve of Milady, 1993; Workers preparing circus outfits, 1991; Worker for "Peter and the Wolf", 1991; Random sample buttons made at Universal, 1994; Workers at Sequins Int'l, 1995; Group learning on-site education, 1995; Worker creates a sequin gown, 1995; Worker in mixing room, 1992; Workers of Bennington Potters, VT., 1991; Workers at American Accents, Bridgeport, PA, 1995; A KT horse, 1994; U.S. Olympic skater Nancy Kerrigan, 1994
- Garment Workers & A Whole Lot More (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Includes Workers at Wondermaid, 1993; The Mothers' House, a shelter for battered woman, San Francisco, CA, 1992; Caring for the elderly, 1992; Home health aides, 1992; Workers at Lion Brothers, Reisterstown, MD, 1992; Workers at Blue Valley Industries, Central PA., 1991; Graphic "Down the aisle with the union label", 1993; Variety of garment worker photos
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Includes 15th Super Sewers class, 1991; Dick Miniscalco, Pres. Philip Pologruto of Frank Mode Inc., Pres. Joseph Maniscalco of Manis Coat Co., State Labor Commissioner Thomas Hartnett, V.P. Peter Ehlinger of Intercontinental Branded Apparel and Pres. Theodore Schatzberg of Party Formals, NYC, n.d.,; Garment Industry Development Corp. (GIDC) pres. Freidman, 1988; Mayor Rudolph Giuliani, Eli Elias, president of the NY Skirt & Sportswear Association, ILGWU Pres. Jay Mazur and GIDC Director Bruce Herman, 1995
- Garment Center Zoning (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Includes GIDC Pres. Harry Schwartz, 1987
- General Advisory Council (GAC) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Includes GAC members at Unity House, 1986; Jose Torres, regional director in Puerto Rico, 1990
- General Executive Board (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Includes Midwest Region Director Stanley Gross, Washington, D.C., 1993; Pres. Jay Mazur, GEB District Council Meeting, San Francisco. CA,1988; Mazur, General Sec'y Treas. Irwin Solomon and Exec. Vice Pres. Wilbur Daniels, Montreal, 1987; Mazur, Solomon, Hollywood, FL., 1987; Mazur, Solomon & Edgar Romney, San Francisco, CA., n.d.; Mazur with Judith Wineman, 1986; Mazur, Solomon, Romney, Wilbur Daniels at GEB meeting, 1987; Mazur, Solomon and former pres. Sol Chaikin at GEB meeting, 1988; Mazur with IP strikers in NY, 1988; General Auditor Milton Spitz announcing his retirement, 1988; International Relations Director Michele Briones, Solomon and Western States Director Steven Nutter, 1988; Mazur with Sol Goldberg, Sal Giardina, new NJ Region director and Barbara Laufman, NYS District Director, 1986
- General Photos (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Includes ILGers pay homage to Triangle Fire victims, n.d.; Rescue workers at the Alfred P. Murrah Federal Building in Oklahoma City, OK. 1995; Students at NY High School of Fashions Industries, 1994; Students leaflet for the ILGWU, NY, 1994; Puppets and sets by Joao Paulo Castano Ferreira and Eleanora Castano Ferreira, 1993; Sec'y Treas Irwin Solomon, 1987; Former Editor Simon Weber, n.d.
- General Photos (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Includes Exec. V.P. Wilbur Daniels, n.d.; Workers at a union shop in the garment district, NY, 1987; Daniels, V.P. Sal Giardian, regional director, Asst. Director Emanuel Leventhal and District Manager Mildred Lippman, 1987; ILGers volunteer their time at local hospital, 1989; ILGWU at NYC's Bellevue Hospital, 1989; Rhea Perlman of "Cheers", 1988; The Italian American Labor Council affair with Giardina, council treasurer Giorgio Benvenuto, IALC Pres. Thomas Rumore and Santo Pernicone, NY, 1987; Farm labor leader Cesar Chavez and Pres. Jay Mazur head rally to boycott A & P supermarkets, NYC, 1986; Mazur and Chavez at AFL-CIO convention, 1987; Former NYC mayor Ed Koch and Mazur at Clothing drive for homeless, NYC, 1987; Graphic for Martin Luther King Jr. birthday, 1987
- General Photos (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Includes Graphic protesting deadly pesticides used in CA., 1987; Immigrants at Ellis Island, 1986; Graphic for Constitution Week, 1989; General Sec'y-Treas. Irwin Solomon announcing Avon boycott, 1988; Tenement museum founding day, 1989; Graphic for "Buy U.S. Savings Bonds, 1987; Graphic for "American Family Celebration", 1988; Graphic to boycott Coors beer, 1987; Japanese evacuated from Bainbridge Island, Washington state, 1987; A. Philip Randolph Institute national conference, St. Louis, MO., 1986; Former Chief Justice Warren, n.d.; Striking CWA workers, NYC, 1986
- General Photos (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Includes ILG exec. V.P. Edgar Romney and GIDC Pres. Bruce Herman at ceremony honoring "super sewers", NYC, 1994; Sec'y-Treas Irwin Solomon and Pres. Jay Mazur honored by the Organization for Rehabilitation, 1993; Daughter of ILGers, 1993; Supreme Court Justice Marshall and wife Cecilia at swearing-in ceremony, 1967; ILGers looking for new voters, 1992; Jobs with Justice rally, NYC, 1988; V.P. Sal Giardina, Emanuel Levanthal and ILGers supporting troops in the Persian Gulf, n.d.; Art by Ralph Fasanella, 1990; ILGers at art show, 1990; Art by Gina Fasanella Mostrando, 1990; ILGers protest Food & Drug Administration (FDA), NY, 1990; Various recipes, 1990; Graphic for "Earth Day", 1990; Graphic for "health benefits" compared to "CPI", n.d.; Collen Powell with mother, 1979; Exec. V.P. Edgar Romney with ILGers at A. Philip Randolph Institute convention, Atlanta, GA.; 1993; Graphic for 1990 census
- Health/Consumer Columns (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Includes Variety of photos of fruits & vegetables, 1994; Variety of sunglasses photos promoting eye protection, 1993; ILGWU's "TB Team, 1992; Variety of graphics from the American Heart Association promoting "good health", 1988; Graphic, "Caring for your baby before birth", 1990; Members from J & J Lingerie, Granville, NY, 1991; ILGers at health center, `1987; Graphic for "Great American Smokeout", 1988; Graphic of "Tips on counting calories, 1986; Students at Cardio-Pulmonary Resuscitation (CPR) course, NYC, 1988; Retiree in ILG exercise class1993
- Health Care Reform (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Includes ILG rally in Los Angeles for health care reform, 1995; Rally for health care reform, NY, 1993; Public Advocate Mark Green and ILGers in protest against Pizza Hut, NY, 1994; President Bill Clinton at health care rally Liberty State Park, NJ, 1994; Commerce Secretary Ron Brown at health care conference, 1994; Cartoons for health care by Huck Konopacki & Carol Simpson respectively, 1994; Health care rally at home of Rep. Helen Bentley, Towson, MD, 1994; Health care really, Duncan, OK., 1994; Fighting healthcare editorial by Pres. Jay Mazur, 1996; Health care rally, Miami, FL., 1994; Health care press conference, NYC, 1994; Tennessee health care rally, 1994; Health care for retirees, FL., 1994; Health care rally, NYC, 1994; Senator Harris Wofford with Central PA. ILGers at health care press conference, n.d.,; ILGers leafleting in York, PA. during Health Care Action Day, n.d.; ILGers rally for AIDS funding and health care reform, 1992; Pres. Jay Mazur, CWA V.P. Jan Pierce, Rep. John Conyers, N.Y. Assemblyman Richard Gottfried, 1993
- Health Care Reform (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Includes - Health care rally, WA, 1993; Sen. Paul Wellstone at rally, Washington, D.C. 1993; ILGers at rally in Washington, D.C., 1993; ILGers voice their concerns at Congressman Tom Manton's town meeting, NYC, 1992; ILGers rally in Newark, NJ; 1991, Congressman Marty Russo at retiree meeting in Chicago, 1992; Assemblyman Richard Gottfried addressing ILGers in NY, 1992; Congressman Carroll Hubbard Jr., Mayfield, KT., 1992 Amira Barros, AIM chapter president, and Jesus Mendez, AIM vice president at town meeting, Brooklyn, NY, 1992; ILG town meeting, NJ, 1992; ILG rally, Harrisburg, PA., n.d.; General Sec'y Treas, Irwin Solomon, 1990; Pres. Jay Mazur at rally, City Hall, NY, 1991; N.H. Rep. Dick Swett, Democratic Rosa DeLauro of CT., Democratic John Murhte of PA, Democrat Austin Murphy of PA., n.d., Rep. Marty Russo and Mazur endorsing "Russo bill", 1991
- Health Care Reform (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Includes - Democrat Bob Toricelli, 1991; Democrat Jose Serrano of NY, 1991; Exec. V.P. Edgar Romney at town meeting, Brooklyn, NY, 1992; Michael Dukakis at ILG town meeting, 1992; Congressman Norman Sisisky, 1992; Frank Hanley, Jay Mazur and AFL-CIO Pres. Lane Kirkland at Rutgers hearing, 1990; Broadcast journalist Walter Cronkite, 1990
- Health & Safety (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Includes Members of Jane and Linda Sportswear take advantage of free mammogram, Lebanon, KT., 1992; Exercise class at Spring Health Conference, 1995; Press conference in support of OSHA, Washington D.C., 1995; Train the trainer workshops, NJ, 1995; ILGers commemorate 1911 Triangle fire and demand OSHA reform, 1992; Cartoon entitled "Needed: Job Safety Reform" by Belland, n.d.; Drawing of a mammogram, 1994; Union workers at rally for "Workers Memorial Day" at Union Square Park, NY, 1993; ESL class on shop safety, 1993
- Health & Safety (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Includes Variety of pictures of workers "in action", 1992; K Mart workers at training session, 1992; Exec. V.P. Edgar Romney at rally, NYC, 1993; ILGers at Southern Illinois rally, 1990; Firefighters battling flames at garment factory, Chinatown, NYC, 1990; AFL-CIO Pres. John Olsen, New Haven, CT., 1990
- Health & Safety (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Includes Northeast Educ. Dir. Hosteller, 1989; Graphic for "Mourn the dead, fight for the living, n.d., Exec. V.P. Edgar Romney at rally, NY, 1989; ILGers learning safety in Evansville, ID., 1987; Graphic for Carpal Tunnel Syndrome, 1987; ILGers at exercise class, NY, 1989
- History in the Making (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Includes President Franklin Delano Roosevelt signing the Social Security Act, August 14, 1935; Women's History, Pauline Newman and Clara Lemich, 1994; Poster "Fight Nazism and Fascism" by Mitchell Loeb, 1993; Dues book from 1907 superimposed over photo of NY's Lower East Side, 1991; AFL Pres. Samuel Gompers, NYC, 1994; Photo showing labor and Truman Administration cross-country tour to promote national health care, 1993; Various "Justice" front covers, 1993; ILGers learning to vote, 1992; The Holocaust Museum, 1993; Photo from the holocaust, 1993; Anita Hill, 1992; Triangle Fire rally, NYC, 1992; Locked exit at Imperial Foods plant, 1992; 1963 March on Washington, 1992; 1983 Nobel Peace Prize winner Lech Walesa, Poland, 1991; Selection of Ernest Fiene's murals, 1991
- Clinton Health Plan (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Includes ILGers rally for health care, NYC, n.d.; Cartoon about "Clinton Health Plan, 1994; Hillary Rodman Clinton testifying to Congress, 1994; Health Care reform rally, western states, 1993; ILGers at GOP fundraiser, NY, 1993; Various pictures of union workers in support of "Clinton Health Plan"
- Homework (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Includes Union members testifying at Los Angeles hearing, 1989; Ca. Attn. Gen'l John Van de Kamp and Beatriz Nava, director of the ILG's L.A. Immigration Project, 1989; Pres. Jay Mazur at New York hearing, 1989; Author Studs Terkel at Chicago homework hearing, 1989; Cartoon for homework by Huck Konopacki, 1988; Jay Mazur, 1988; Graphic for the "Great American Smokeout, 1987; Arguing against "industrial homework", 1987; Various letters from organizations & individuals regarding "homework", 1987; ILGers writing letters to the Dept. of Labor, 1986; ILGers at the Illinois State AFL-CIO Convention, 1986; Testimony before House Subcommittee on Labor Standards, 1986; Article by Pres. Jay Mazur, 1986
- Housing Homeless (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Includes ILGers from Easton, PA. District Council with banners at rally, 1988; Various pictures of the homeless
- ILGWU Chorus (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Includes ILGWU Chorus signing in NYC, n.d
- ILG History (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Includes (newspaper clippings only) ILG graphic "Constitution of the United, Brotherhood of Cloakmakers', Union #1, 1995; Cartoon by Bernard Seamons shows conversion back to domestic fashions, 1995; ILG graphic celebrating "95 years", 1995; Graphic by Tracy Sugarman depicting the 1958 dress industry strike, 1995; 1982 Contract dispute, ILGers in NY's Chinatown, 1995; Jay Mazur at rally; 1963 March on Washington, 1995; David Dubinsky "breaking ground" for housing project in Puerto Rico, 1995; Ladies Garment Worker, the forerunner of Justice, 1995; ILG toddlers in CT. (1941), 1995; St. Louis picnic raised money for strikers in Cleveland, 1995; Outdoor lecture at Unity House, PA, 1995; 1909 shirtwaist strike, 1995; Strike called in English, Italian and Yiddish, 1995; Cartoon, helped galvanize outrage over the Triangle fire, 1995; First Lady Eleanor Roosevelt, 1995; Justice, 1995; Post war campaign, Appomattox, VA., 1995; The ILF reaffiliated with the AFL in 1940 and worked for reunification, 1995; Cleveland workers march on City Hall, 1995; 1972 import demo across the country, 1995; 1958 dressmakers strike, 1995;Credo, "Knowledge is Power", 1995; Graphic for 1937 ILGWU pledge, "Ever to go Onward", 1995; Musical, "Pins and Needles", with ILGers in the roles, 1995; Franklin D. Roosevelt and ILG. Pres David Dubinsky at the White House, n.d.; (remaining are photos) ILG Pres. Jay Mazur, former ILG Secretary-Treasurer Shelley Appleton and AFL-CIO Secretary-Treasurer Thomas Donahue, 1993; Scenes of "Pins and Needles" at the Washington Jewish Theater, n.d.; Various pictures from Ellis Island, n.d.
- Immigration (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Includes Jay Mazur at the Somerset Knitting Mall, PA.; Mazur, NY Ex-Mayor David Dinkins and Elizabeth Aivers, director of the Mayor's Office of Immigrant Affairs, 1993; United Farm Workers (UFW) Pres. Cesar Chavez, Mazur at Columbus Circle, NYC in solidarity with farm workers, 1993; Temporary resident license, 1989; Asian Labor Festival, NY, 1990; Jeff Stansbury, political/education director of the ILGWU Western States Region, 1987; Cartoon about "amnesty", n.d., Exec. V.P. Wilbur Daniels, 1987; ILGWU attorney Catherine Waelder, NY, 1987; NY staffers at training session, 1987; Exec. V.P. Daniels, 1987; May Chen of the ILGWU Immigration Project, Boston, MA., 1987; Cartoon about the Immigration Bill by Huck Konopacki, 1986; Conducting workshop for organizers, 1987
- Import Rollback Campaign (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Includes - Central PA. ILGers lobby to "Veto the Textile Bill", Washington D.C., (circa 1990's); Pres Jay Mazur with ILGers, Washington, D.C., (circa 1990's) House of Representatives speaker Jim Wright, (1980's);Research director Dr. Herman Starobin before the trade subcommittee, (1980's); Exec. V.P. Edgar Romney, 1986; Florida Governor Bob Graham with ILGers, Florida, 1986; Western region ILGers protest, 1986; Leafletting in Atlanta, 1986; ILGers outside Oakley Fashions, Tenn., 1986; Ed Pulver, Sec'y Treasurer NJ AFL-CIO, and ILGers in parade, Union City, NJ, 1986
- International Relations & Affairs (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Includes ILGers await South Africa's Nelson Mandela's visit to America, 1995; Garment workers in El Salvador, 1995; Strikers in El Salvador, 1995; Chile's top leader Manuel Bustos, 1995; Demonstrators in front of the Sony Building, NY, 1994; South African unionists from House of Monatic, 1993; ILG Exec. Pres. Edgar Romney and Immigration Project Director Muzaffar Chishti, 1993; Child labor, Pakistan, 1993; Pres. Jay Mazur, 1995; ILGers of South Africa's Chemical Workers' Union, 1994; Self-Employed Women's Association, India, 1992; New York firm woo Japanese fashion buyers, 1991; Honduran girls, making sweaters for Liz Claiborne, 1994; Workers in Cite Soleil, Port-au-Prince, 1993; Unionists in South Africa, 1993; Workers in China, Hong Kong, 1992; Haitian refugees, Cuba, 1992; AFL-CIO subcommittee in China, 1992; Jose Ramirez, president of the regional textile and apparel workers organization, 1992
- International Relations & Affairs (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Includes - Pres. Jay Mazur protesting government's policy of sending back Haitian refugees, 1992; Milka Tyszkiewicz, a Solidarity activist in Poland, 1990; Mazur and CWA Pres. Morton Bahr, 1991; Russian unionists, NY, 1991; Graphic for "Proposed free trade agreement", 1991; southern Africa unionists, Lesotho, 1991; Nelson Mandela, 1990; Rally at Yankee stadium, 1990; Exec. V.P. Edgar Romney and Mandela at AFL-CIO, Washington D.C., 1990; ILGers at Mandela rally, 1990; Jay Mazur at China's U.N. Mission, 1990; Students at press conference in Tiananmen Square, 1990; Mazur and [?} Rojas, 1990; Election in Chile, (circa 1990's); Solidarity leader Lech Walesa and V.P. Joseph Fisher at ILGWU headquarters, Philadelphia, PA., (1990's), Protestors, El Salvador, (1990's); Aurtuo Martinez, n.d.; Manuel Bustos, n.d.; ILGers protest Brazilian government, 1989; Workers in Cairo, 1989
- International Relations & Affairs (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Includes Child laborers, Bangladesh, 1993; Earthquake in El Salvador, 1986; Children rescued by the South Asian Coalition on Child Servitude, 1993; Indian child labor activist Kalish Satyarthi, 1993; Child labor in Korea, 1988; Pres. Jay Mazur and Amon Ntuli, president of ACTWUSA, the South African textile and garment workers union, 1988; Adams Oshiomhole, Secretary-General of Nigerian garment workers' union, PA., 1988; Carmen Muriana Ramirez, head of the Women's Dept. at the UGT, Spain, 1988; Michele Briones, director of the International Relations Dept. and Associate Political-Education Director, Saul Rosen, 1988; Pres. Mazur and Sol Chaikin, 1986; Saul Rosen, El Salvador, 1987; Workers in South Africa, 1988; Vice Pres, Joseph Fisher, of PA. region and Honduran Pres. Roberto Suazo Cordova, 1987; Moses Nhlapo, organizing-treasurer of the Transvaal region's Textile Workers Union of South Africa with General Sec'y-Treas. Irwin Solomon, 1987; The Nigerian, Textile, Garment and Tailoring Workers convention, 1986; Pres. Mazur, V.P. Sam Fine, manager of NY Local 91-105 with Rita Schneider, widow of ILGWU V.P. Edward Schneider, 1986; Walter Mankoff, associate director of the ILG's Research Dept., NY, 1986; Japanese trade unionists, NY, 1986; Jamaican union leaders in the Midwest, 1986; Workers at Home Schiffon Garments Mfg., Panang, Malaysia, 1986; Workers at the Fu Yuen garment factory, Castle Peak, Hong Kong, 1986; New England Educational Director, Carl Proper, 1986; The Royal Dutch/Shell Group of Companies Alternative Corporate Report, 1987
- Label Dept. & Promotion (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Includes Members of the ILGWU chorus who appeared in a commercial, 1991; Pres. Jay Mazur with ILGers in Kansas City, Kansas, 1986; ILGWU chorus in Philadelphia, PA, 1987; Members of the Tokunaga Dance Ko of NYC wearing ILGWU t-shirts, 1987; AFL-CIO annual Union-Industries show, Atlantic City, NJ, 1987; ILGWU label, 1987; All-American fashion show, NYC, 1987; Beverly Shulman, director of the Union Label Dept., 1987; Cast of "Look the Union Label", 1989; ILGers in pose for union poster, 1988
- Labor Day Parade (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Includes 1992 parade, NYC; ILGers at 1990 parade; ILGWU strikers from Teammate at 1989 parade; ILGers at 1988 parade; Pres. Jay Mazur leading 1988 parade
- Labor Day Parade (Box 7, Folder 8)
  Includes ILGers at 1987 parade; ILGers at 1992 parade; ILGers at 1987 parade with "Look for the Union Label" banner, International ILGers at 1987 parade; ILGers at 1988 parade; Jay Mazur, Exec. Vice Pres. Edgar Romney, Raymond O'Kane, Paschal McGuinness, and NYC Central Labor Council Pres. Thomas Van Arsdale and Brian McLaughlin, 1988; ILGWU chorus at Grand Central Station, 1990; 1986 parade, St. Louis, MO., 1986 parade, Fall River, MA.; 1986 parade, Chicago, Ill., ILG Western PA. District Council Manager Yvonne
- Labor Day Parade (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Includes 1986 parade, Philadelphia, PA; 1994 parade, CT.; 1994 parade, Chicago, Ill.; AIM members, Williamsburg, Brooklyn; ILGers at 1992 parade; ILGers with banner at 1989 parade; ILGers celebrate 90th anniversary of ILGWU at 1989 parade; ILGers at 1990; 1989 parades in Chicago, Philadelphia and NYC; Exec. VP Edgar Romney at 1990 parade
- Labor History (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Includes (newspaper clippings and photos) Dressmakers at Madison Square Garden during 1933 general strike, 1991; ILGers striking in Toronto against the Eaton Co. in 1912, 1991; Mrs. Franklin Delano Roosevelt (circa 1940's), 1991; Strikers at the Kalamazoo Corset Shop, 1912; 1987; Drawing of 1886 Haymarket riot, 1986; Meeting of Patterson NJ silk strikers at Botto House, Haledon, NY, 1913
- Labor Law History (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Includes Unionists protest National Labor Relations Board (NLRB), San Francisco, CA., 1993; ILGers protest outside Domsey, La Mode, CA., 1993; Unionists arguing with NLRB, Cleveland, OH., 1993; Unionist demonstrate at NLRB, Fort Worth, TX., 1993; ILGers protest, Tulsa, OK, 1993
- Leaders on the Line (Box 8, Folder 4)